Drew Knutson

(651) 261-8746 | d.s.grondahl01@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/drew-knutson | dgrondahl.com

Profile

A results-oriented team player who can quickly pick up on new concepts and ideas. Is capable of effectively working with multiple clients/companies at the same time and prioritizing workloads. An accomplished developer with experience in CRM configuration, Object-Oriented Programming, and web design/programming. Has a history of both programming and photo/video editing professionally, with a passion for both.

Experience

Associate Technical Consultant | Perficient inc. | 2023 - Present

- · Gather requirements, design, code, beta test, deploy, and maintain projects from start to finish
- · Assist business lines with solving technical problems quickly and efficiently
- · Prepared and presented to clients system demonstrations of processes and functionality implemented
- · Follow change management procedures across services such as GitHub, Copado, and Jira
- · Stay up to date with new Salesforce releases to determine the impact on client orgs

STUDENT SUPERVISOR | NDSU IT DEPARTMENT | 2020 - 2023

- · Manage a team of six students made up of both undergraduate and international graduate students
- · Compile the team's weekly schedule, including shifts, workshops, and project deadlines
- · Assign project work to team members and ensure it will be completed on time and to a high standard
- Help students and staff who come in with IT issues and specific issues in the Adobe Suite, Davinci Resolve, and Audacity

LIFEGUARD | YMCA - HUDSON WI | 2018 - 2022

- · Supervise all pools and ensure that all patrons follow the rules and remain safe
- · Be ready to assist in or take charge of an emergency throughout the facility

Education

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE - COMPUTER SCIENCE, MINOR - HISTORY | NORTH DAKOTA STATE UNIVERSITY

Skills & Abilities

- · Proficient in Java, HTML, APEX, SOQL
- Experience in SQL, CSS, C, C#, JavaScript, TypeScript, Python
- · Agile software development
- · VS Code, Github, Copado
- · Salesforce configuration

Activities and Interests

History, programming, hiking, travel, photography